352-665-1142 <a href="https://paradegoat.github.io/portfolio">https://paradegoat.github.io/portfolio</a> humphreys.geoff@gmail.com

## **Profile**

A community-minded innovator and thought explorer. More than a decade of starting and managing businesses has taught me that working with a team of smart, kind people to create an awesome experience for others is my idea of a good life.

## **Skills**

Ruby on Rails | Javascript | HTML | CSS3 | Node.js | MySql | PostgreSql | MongoDB | Git | Responsive Web Design | RESTful APIs

# **Education**

The Iron Yard, Durham, NC — Backend Engineering Certificate, 2017 Santa Fe College, Gainesville, FL — Associate of Arts in American History

# **Experience**

Owner Operator Founder, Taradiddle Design Inc — 2015 - Present

- \* Collaborated with clients to design and build over a dozen dream spaces, including an arcade bar, a event space and music venue, an upscale cocktail lounge, kitchen remodels, and a free-standing yoga pavilion.
- \* Directed day-to-day operations, including all accounting and banking duties, managing & coordinating subcontractors, filing permit applications, scheduling inspections, & shop and equipment maintenance.
- \* Researched and applied, when safe and legal, all electrical, plumbing and structural knowledge as needed to reduce cost to the client and increase company marketability

## Store Operator, Pop-A-Top — 2013 - 2015

- \* Designed, opened and supervised a corner store in a high traffic downtown which generated \$250,00 in the first year, with continued growth month over month.
- \* Oversaw day-to-day operations, including tracking inventory, submitting product orders, coordinating with distributors and local suppliers, and directed a team of 6 employees by creating weekly schedules and task lists and developing a framework to maintain regular and honest communication.

# Owner Operator Founder, Boca Fiesta/Backyard — 2009 - 2013

- \* Designed, built and managed a restaurant, bar and outdoor event hall with annual revenues of over \$1,000,000 and more than 50 employees.
- \* Developed and operated the online marketing strategy, including all social media accounts and maintenance of the organization website.
- \* Organized and coordinated daily events at the 300 person outdoor concert hall, including live music, art and film exhibits, and events with community leaders and political committees.
- \* Supervised front and back of house team leaders to ensure good communication among all team members and efficient and effective time management.

## Store Operator, Lightnin' Salvage Junk Museum — 2004-2009

- \* Transformed a popular restaurants' unused building into an art museum, gift shop and waiting lounge to reduce the loss of business due to frequently long wait times.
- \* Responsible for discovering new artists and collaborating to showcase collections, performance pieces and live music.
- \* Managed day-to-day operations of the gift shop including logging daily sales, ordering and organizing new products, and general store maintenance